hey everybody welcome back to the show
folks my next guest is a stand-up
comedian and host of my favorite late
night show in China is it true please
welcome all the way from Beijing Joe
Wong
[Applause]
[Music]
hi buddy give up there hello so I am
actually an American immigrant and they
say that America is a country of
immigrants so I have to ask you guys
please leave my country I'm serious we
have a zero-tolerance policy right now I
heard that our ages have become the
fastest growing immigrant group in
America which is really amazing because
Mexicans can cross the river and come
here and I have to fly thousands of
miles to Mexico
[Laughter]
[Applause]
and then cross that river swamp wants to
build a wall to stop immigration I'm
from China so I know a lot about walls
they don't work
and centrist later it's just going to
become a huge tourist attraction but I
do respect from though because after he
took office there is the KKK March anti
KKK March when this Marsh anti-child
separation March and you know how much
Americans hate exercise
[Laughter]
he has contributed more to America's
health that all the YMCA's combines and
he also contributes to the health of
other countries because laughter is the
best medicine
I mean have you seen his performance at
you and he killed there probably even a
better audience the new guys are just
kidding you guys are great my son was
born and raised in America I remember
one day he came home he came home from
school that was when he was about 5
years old he said to me hey Dad
I learned American history today I said
wow that's great he said now I really
feel bad for black people
I said yeah there really must witted in
American history
he's a year and I'm so glad that I'm
white
I was the hold on you're not wait he
said that what am i I said your yellow
this true story that he like take a look
at his hand he was like daddy
this doesn't look yellow to me I said
yes I know but this is America and
everybody has to have a color and that's
the color that gave us you better deal
with it but my son has a good point
though nobody in America especially a
person of color is exactly the color
they're assigned you know like this is
not exactly yellow it's kind of brown a
black person is not exactly black
they're kind of brown so we're pretty
much all different shades of Mexicans
[Laughter]
so why people please don't feel left out
I have a lot a lot of things in common
with white guys for example I have an
Asian wife
[Applause]
[Music]
so long everybody